http://www.activeendeavors.com/pages/privacy-policy

HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Credit Card InformationYour credit card is charged as you submit your order only for the amount you have approved. Refunds for returned products or unavailable items are processed with the same credit card that was provided in the original order. At no point does Active Endeavors possess the full credit card number unless given to it during a manual transaction, such as a phone order. A short period of time after the order is processed, the credit card information is purged from the order.E-mail Notifications/Opting OutCustomers that place an order may receive notifications of new arrivals, discounts and updated information from our Site. Even if you opt out, you may continue to receive non-marketing e-mail messages from us including, for example, communications regarding your order. You may "Opt Out" of receiving these e-mails by using the "Unsubscribe Me" link at the bottom of every e-mail. Customer Service may also use your e-mail address to contact you about abandoned shopping carts or uncompleted orders. It may be necessary to contact affiliates, business partners or other third parties directly in order to cease receiving communications from those third parties.Information We CollectWe may obtain personal information about you from various sources, including this and our other websites, mobile applications, when you call or email us or communicate with us through social media, or when you participate in events or other promotions. We also may obtain information about you from our business partners and other third parties. Any personal information you provide to us is maintained on secure servers and our internal systems.Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our sites. This includes personalization services, interactive communications, online shopping and many other types of services, all of which are completely free to you.CookiesCookies are a message that a web server transmits to a web browser to personalize the user's experience on our Site. Cookies can help store Personal Information about you so that when you return to the Site you have a more personalized experience. Have you ever returned to a site and have seen your name mysteriously appear on the screen? It is because on a previous visit you gave your name to the site and it was stored in a cookie so that when you returned you would be greeted with a personal message. Cookies do not act maliciously on computer systems. They are merely text files that you have the option of deleting at any time. All browsers can be set to reject cookies if the user prefers to use the Internet without enabling cookies to be stored. Please note that certain features of the checkout process may require you to enable Cookies on your browser.Legal DisclosureWe reserve the right to monitor, and disclose to government officials or law enforcement, without your consent, any communications and personally identifiable information, whenever prompted to do so by legal authorities, even when you have requested that your information not be disclosed to third parties. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved. The contents of activeendeavors.com are provided "AS IS" and may contain errors or inaccuracies and may not be complete or current (we strive for 100% accuracy but we are only human). We reserve the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions (including after an order has been submitted) and to modify, change or update information (including pricing and/or product code numbers), at any time without prior notice. We may terminate your access to or suspend your right to access all or part of activeendeavors.com, without notice, for any conduct that we believe is in violation of any applicable law or is harmful to the interests of our Site. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time and will post any changes to this policy on their effective date.Active Endeavors Text OffersActive Endeavor’s customers may opt-in to receive promotional marketing SMS & MMS messages from Active Endeavors Text Offers via shortcode 35945. Active Endeavor customers can opt-in by texting “GetActive” to 35945. By opting-in to receive recurring SMS and MMS messages from Active Endeavors Text Offers, the subscriber consents to receive pre-written marketing messages from short code 35945 on behalf of Active Endeavors Text Offers, acknowledges that message and data rates may apply and understands that consent is not a condition of purchase. Active Endeavors Text Offers’s privacy policy can be viewed at https://www.activeendeavors.com/privacypolicy.aspxOPT-OUT INSTRUCTIONSYou can opt-out of receiving future text messages by replying to 35945 using any of the following words: STOP, END, QUIT, CANCEL, UNSUBSCRIBE. Standard carrier rates apply.HELP INSTRUCTIONSReply “HELP” to 35945 at any time to receive mobile customer service information. (844)-558-6766 or support@toitech.co for more information.CURRENT KEYWORDSGETACTIVE, HELP, STOP, END, QUIT, CANCEL, UNSUBSCRIBEParticipating Wireless CarriersPlease be advised that mobile carriers are not responsible for delayed or undelivered messages.Active Endeavor’s Text Offers is compatible with all major wireless carriers, including:* AT&T* Verizon Wireless* Sprint* T-Mobile®* Metro PCS* U.S. Cellular®* Many other smaller/regional carriersThe website for Active Endeavors Text Offers, LLC is found at www.activeendeavors.com which is used solely for informational, marketing and promotional purposes. Updated September 27, 2018
TOP
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
View all products
Empty result
MY BAG
SUBTOTAL
Spend $50.00 to Free Shipping
PROCEED TO CHECKOUT
VIEW SHOPPING BAG
Your shopping bag is empty.
MY WISH LIST
VIEW WISH LIST
Your wish list is empty.
MY ACCOUNT
SIGN UP
Enjoy the benefits of registering: Order: view Order History, track and manage purchases and returns Address Book and Card Wallet: safely store delivery and payment details for faster checkout Saved for later: wish list your preferred items and track their availability
Sign up now!
SIGN UP
Thanks for subscribing! Use code: AE93 to take 10% off your purchase*Offer valid on full-price items; U.S. only. Must be new email subscriber. Enter your email address to receive a promo code in your inbox. Additional terms may apply.
Continue shopping
This is an approximate conversion table to help you find your size. If you have already purchased an item by our brand, we recommend you select the same size as indicated on its label.
Women’s apparel sizing
INTERNATIONALXSSMLXLXXLXXXL
EUROPE32343638404244
US024681012
CHEST FIT (INCHES)28"30"32"34"36"38"40"
CHEST FIT (CM)71676818691.596.5101.1
WAIST FIR (INCHES)21"23"25"27"29"31"33"
WAIST FIR (CM)53.558.563.568.5747984
HIPS FIR (INCHES)33"34"36"38"40"42"44"
HIPS FIR (CM)81.586.591.596.5101106.5111.5
SKORT LENGTHS (SM)36.53839.54142.54445.5
Men’s apparel sizing
INTERNATIONALXSSMLXLXXLXXXL
EUROPE32343638404244
US024681012
CHEST FIT (INCHES)33-35"36-38"39-41"42-44"45-47"48-50"51-53"
CHEST FIT (CM)84-8991-9788-104107-112114-119122-127129-134
WAIST FIR (INCHES)28"30"32"34"36"38"40"
WAIST FIR (CM)7176818691.596.5101.5
SKORT LENGTHS (SM)7677.5798182.58485.5
CHEST: Around the fullest part of the neck, at the base. WAIST: Around the narrowest part of the waist. HIPS: Around the widest point of the hips. SKORT LENGTHS: From the crotch to the anklebone on the inside of the leg.
ShippingFree 2-Day Shipping on orders $50 or more (*Excludes over-sized items)In-store pick up is available in the cart page of checkout processNext-day and Express delivery options also availablePurchases are delivered through USPS priority mailSee the delivery FAQs for details on shipping methods, costs and delivery timesReturns And ExchangesReturns can be made 30 days within purchaseSee conditions and procedure in our return FAQs
WISH LIST AND COMPARE
Do you want to add products to your personal account?
YES
NO
This is a standard cookie notice which you can easily adapt or disable as you like in the admin. We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website.
PRIVACY POLICY
ACCEPT
